

Profile

I really want to explore my professional profile as a **front-end / cross-platform developer / designer** and I have the skills to manage, develop and coordinate innovative, sustainable and interdisciplinary projects in different areas of audiovisual creation and programming.

Contact



@art.nitro



linkedin.com/in/isabelandaluz



+34 644 34 23 20



isabelandaluz@hotmail.com



Alcorcón, Madrid

More information

- Date of birth: 06/23/2001
- Driving license.
- Leisure and free time monitor course | In progress.
- Complete availability.

Recognitions

"Dalí & Éluard: Gala's gaze".

Research work selected for the IV Complutense Pre-University Meeting of Young Researchers "With talent from High School."

Isabel Andaluz Fernández

Cross-platform Developer | Digital & Graphic Designer

Education

Professional training degree in Multiplatform application development

CES Juan Pablo II | September 2023 - In process

Design degree

Faculty of Fine Arts, Complutense University of Madrid | September 2019 - July 2023

Baccalaureate of Excellence

San Mateo Institute | September 2017 - May 2019

Experience

Graphic Designer | Internship

Brand Dawson | July 2023 - August 2023 | Getafe, Madrid

- Brand management and digital marketing solutions.
- Design of corporate content: banners, presentations, videos.
- · Management of client social profiles.
- Design of new websites and modifications of current websites.
- Management of paid campaigns (Google Ads and Facebook Ads).
- Preparation of reporting.

Sales assistant

MUNICH | December 2021 - February 2022 | Leganés, Madrid

- Visual organization of the product in the store.
- Teamwork and development of communication.

Sales assistant | Videogames department

El Corte Inglés | Julio 2020 - Mayo 2021 | Arroyomolinos, Madrid

• Creation of the visual image of the store (Visual Merchandising).

Technical skills

Adobe package domain:

















Various design applications domain: Autodesk Sketchbook, Procreate, Krita, Canva, Figma, DALL-E 2, Wix.

Social skills: sales, customer service, teamwork, social networks.

Language skills

English: Advanced level.

"First Certificate" title, Cambridge Institute. Level B2.

German: Basic level.

Two german courses at San Mateo Institute. Level A1.2.

Spanish: Native.